Imagine a future where all farming is done by machine, and humans never set foot in the fields.
想象一下这样一个未来：所有的农业生产都由机器完成，人类再也不用踏入农田。
No, it‘s not science fiction.
不，这不是科幻小说。
In Shropshire in the UK, engineers in the Hands Free Hectare project are developing automated tractors and fleets of drones to grow and harvest crops.
在英国的什罗普郡，“免耕公顷项目”的工程师们正在研发用于种植和收割农作物的自动化拖拉机和无人机机群。
And their experiment is not alone: agricultural robotics is a booming sector.
而且他们的实验并非个例：农业机器人领域正在蓬勃发展。
Investment bank Goldman Sachs estimates the market will be worth $240bn over the next five years.
高盛投资银行预估，在未来五年内，这个市场的价值将达到2400亿美元。
One reason why the sector is on the up is that global demand for food is rapidly increasing.
这个领域不断发展的一个原因是全球对粮食的需求正在迅速增长。
The World Bank estimates we will need to produce 50% more food by 2050 if the planet’s population continues to grow at its current speed.
世界银行估计，如果地球人口继续以目前的速度增长，到2050年我们将需要多生产50%的粮食。
Add to this the forecast that yields will decrease by over a quarter due to climate change, and the situation looks serious.
再加上预计由于气候变化，粮食产量将减少超过四分之一，情况看起来非常严峻。
Could futuristic farming provide the answer?
未来农业能解决这个问题吗？
One company in Japan believes so.
日本的一家公司认为可以。
The firm Spread has dispensed with farming on land altogether, and instead grows vegetables on stacks of trays indoors in an automated factory.
Spread公司已经完全摒弃了在土地上耕种的方式，而是在自动化工厂里一层层的托盘上种植蔬菜。
“In countries like Japan, where land is actually a very scarce resource, it makes more sense to stack your production, just like a skyscraper,” says JJ Price, Spread‘s global marketing manager.
“像日本这样的国家，土地实际上是非常稀缺的资源，像摩天大楼一样把种植堆叠起来是更加明智的做法。”Spread公司的全球营销经理JJ·普莱斯说。
Mr Price told the BBC that this method of vertical farming not only reduces costs by 50%, but it is also greener.
普莱斯先生告诉BBC，这种垂直农业方式不仅能将成本降低50%，而且更环保。
LED lights cut energy bills by a third, and 98% of water can be recycled.
LED灯能将能源费用削减三分之一，并且98%的水可以被循环利用。
By growing crops close to where people consume them, transport costs and emissions are also minimised, he says.
他说，通过在人们消费产品的地方附近种植农作物，运输成本和排放也被降到了最低。
They hope to be producing 30,000 lettuces per day next year.
他们希望明年每天能生产3万颗生菜。
And where will we buy this futuristic food?
那我们在哪里能购买这种未来食物呢？
Perhaps in shops with no staff?
也许是在没有员工的商店里？
Amazon has recently launched its first Amazon Go store in the US, which has no checkouts.
亚马逊最近在美国推出了第一家Amazon Go商店，这家商店没有收银台。
Customers simply pick their items from the shelves, and technology does the rest.
顾客只需从货架上挑选商品，剩下的都由科技来完成。
All this begs the question: if everything is automated, what jobs will people do?
所有这些都引出了一个问题：如果一切都自动化了，人们将从事什么工作呢？
The mechanisation of farming means fewer and fewer people work the land.
农业的机械化意味着在土地上劳作的人越来越少。
From 1950 to 2010, agricultural labourers have decreased from 81% to 48.2% of the workforce in developing countries, and from 35% to 4.2% in developed countries, according to the International Labour Organization.
根据国际劳工组织的数据，从1950年到2010年，发展中国家农业劳动力占劳动力总数的比例从81%下降到了48.2%，发达国家则从35%下降到了4.2%。
It’s a trend that looks set to continue.
这一趋势预计还将持续下去。